<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">
    
    <string name="app_name">SuperGenPass</string>
	<string name="domain_description">Site\'s domain:</string>
	<string name="domain_hint">example.org</string>
	<string name="password_description">Master password:</string>
	<string name="go">Go!</string>
	<string name="copy">Copy</string>
	<string name="password_output_label">Generated password: </string>
	<string name="password_hint">master password</string>
	
	<string name="sgp_type">SuperGenPass</string>
	<string name="pwc_type">Password Composer</string>
	
	<string name="app_description">Password hashing tool.</string>
	<string name="err_no_md5">Error finding MD5 implementation: %1$s</string>
	<string name="toast_copied">Password for %1$s copied to clipboard.</string>
	
	<string name="preferences">SuperGenPass Preferences</string>
	<string name="user_preferences">User Preferences</string>
	<string name="advanced_preferences">Advanced Preferences</string>
	
	<string name="pwgen_type_prompt">Password generator type</string>
	<string name="pwgen_type_description">Password Composer is a simpler algorithm that generates weaker passwords. SuperGenPass is recommended.</string>
	<string name="pwgen_type_summary">Lets you pick a password generating algorithm other than SuperGenPass.</string>
	 
	<string name="pref_copy_password">Copy gen\'d password</string>
	<string name="pref_copy_password_summary">When the Go button is pressed, copy the generated password.</string>
	
	<string name="pref_pw_length">Generated password length</string>
	<string name="pref_pw_length_description">This should be value between 4 and 24. A value of 10 for SGP and 8 for PWC is highly recommended for compatibility with the other implementations.</string>
	
	<string name="about_title">About SuperGenPass</string>
	<string name="about_text">
SuperGenPass is a different kind of password manager: instead of randomly generating and storing passwords, it combines a Web site's domain and your master password to generate a unique password for each Web site you visit using a strong cryptographic hash.
 
In addition to launching it directly, in the Browser activity, go to: Menu → More → Share Page. 

To use on your computer, please see the parent project: SuperGenPass.com. This has both a handy bookmarklet as well as a stand-alone Javascript page.

This project is Free Software/Open Source and is licensed under the GNU GPL Version 3. You can get the source for this application from http://staticfree.info/projects/sgp/

Final word of caution: while SGP generates strong passwords, if a malicious Web site knows that you're using SGP and has access to the plain-text of your password for their site, they could potentially brute-force your master password. Therefore it is recommended to make sure your master password is also strong. One great technique for such a password is to use the first letters of a favorite phrase. For example, \"When on Earth, do as the humans do?\" becomes \"W0EdatHd\". 
</string>
</resources>
